Contact

lauraann01@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/laura-demello-85375834 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Patient Safety
Critical Care Nursing
Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation
(CPR)

Certifications

Advance Cardiac Life Support
Basic Life Support
Certified Emergency Nurse
Pediatric Advanced Life Support

Laura Demello

Emergency Nursing. BSN, RN, CEN Cape Coral, Florida

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Experienced emergency nurse and leader of the medical emergency response team in an acute care hospital setting. Skilled in patient advocacy, patient education, cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR), and advanced cardiac life support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Nursing from University of Massachusetts Dartmouth.

Experience

Lee Health
Registered Nurse
July 2013 - Present (7 years 1 month)
Fort Myers, Florida Area

Southcoast Hospitals Group Registered Nurse November 2011 - June 2013 (1 year 8 months)

Education

University of Massachusetts Dartmouth BSN, Nursing

Bristol Community College ADN, Nursing

Chamberlain University

Master's degree, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2019 - 2021)